Hi, this is Eric.  Let's talk about
FWD's set for health.  Seth is a
traditional life insurance plan.  That
means it's not VOL.  It has no
investment component.  This plan
has three key major benefits.  Number
one is the life insurance benefit.
Number two is the critical illness benefit.
And number three, his return of
premium benefit.  The age to
take out this plan is 15 days old
to 60 years old.  That depends on the
paying period we take.  The
paying period available is 5 years to
pay, 10 years to pay and 20 years to pay.   Let's
talk about its
benefits.  Number one is the major
critical illness benefit.  We can
claim up to three times our
coverage if we are diagnosed with major
illnesses such as cancer, major organ
failure, heart attack, etc.  For more
detailed information,
the link attached to the caption of this video is the
official brochure of FWD and even
their policy provisions.  Number two
benefit is the waiver of premium.  If
we are diagnosed with any major
critical illness covered by this policy,
our insurance plan payments will stop.  But
our coverage continues until age 75.
Number three benefit is minor
critical illness.  We will receive
20% of our major critical illness
coverage.  When we are diagnosed with a
minor critical illness,
our major critical
illness coverage is not reduced.  For example,
our major critical illness coverage is 1
million.  So 20% of 1 million is 200,000.
So that's what will be given to us in case
we are diagnosed with a minor critical
illness.  Please note that this is a one-time
claim only or lump sum.  Benefit number four is
of course life insurance or
the death benefit.  If
we ever expire in this world,
our beneficiary will receive money or proceeds.  How much?
Whatever our major critical illness
coverage is, that is also the amount
that will be given to our beneficiary.  Number
five, the healthy life benefit.  This is
what we said earlier, return of
premium.  If
God wills that we live
long, live healthy, and
reach or exceed the
age of 75, we will receive everything
we have lost.
Provided, we have not had any claims for
major critical illness.  Some call
that backsliding.
became a gamble.  Many policy
holders took it because
they were so impressed with the benefits.
Especially the up to three times that
you can claim for major
critical illness.  So they took it.
But I want to make
you understand something important.
This is often not emphasized by
insurance agents.  Reasons for denying
our claims.  So
we have no choice but to just watch and
listen to me.  So these are the
important things we need to
understand.  Number one, we can only
avail up to three times the
critical illness benefit if
he comes from a different group.
Major critical illness is divided
into different groups.  The full details
of that are in the brochure and in the
policy provisions.  Number
two important thing
we must understand.  We can only
claim the following critical illness
benefit.  The second critical
illness benefit is if the interval between
consecutive diagnoses of major
critical illness is at least one year.
So first tell that critical
illness that's knocking.  Don't do it yet.
You're next year.
Number three, we can claim
twice under the cancer group
provided the first diagnosis was declared
cancer free for at least 5 years
before the next cancer diagnosis.
Number four.  If our first diagnosis
is immediate terminal illness or loss
of independent existence, we will no longer be
able to claim subsequent
major critical illness benefits.  Number
five, our claims are based on the
definition and conditions of each
critical illness written in the policy
contract.  This cannot be based solely
on our own definition or our
own research or
our own feelings.  It sounds like a false alarm.
Or number five important thing
we must understand.  There are
possibilities that our
critical illness claims will be denied if it is
related to the number one reason that we were diagnosed
with a critical illness less than 90 days
from the time our insurance plan became effective
.  So there is something called a 90 day
waiting period.  So within those 90 days
, in the first 90 days, there should be no
claims for major critical illness because
otherwise he will not be covered.  Number
two, we have a pre-existing
condition before we apply
this product.  A pre-existing condition is a
health condition that
already exists in us, in
our body, whether we know it or not.
We don't get regular
checkups.  Right.  We may have a
pre-existing one before we apply for
it.  And if that is detected by the
insurance company, it is likely that
our claims will be denied.
Unless we declare him and
the insurance company sees that
they can take the risk, they can
accept the risk, then he is covered.
Number three, we attempted
suicide because during
that attempt we developed a major critical
illness.  That's not covered.  Number four,
we participated in illegal and
unlawful activities.  Number five,
we are addicted to drug use or
we are addicted to alcohol use or
excessive drunkenness.  Due to excessive
intoxication, he caused a major
critical illness, that is not covered.
Number six, if we have HIV or
we acquired HIV before the
critical illness, next, if
we participated in war, civil war,
in extreme unrest, corruption,
etc.  Next number seven.  On the important
thing we must understand.
We only have a 31-day grace
period to pay our
insurance juice from the due date.  If
we can't pay this, these are the things that
could happen to our policy.  Number
one, our coverage will still continue,
but the coverage will decrease based on how
much we have paid in total.  That's
called reduced paid up coverage.
Number two,
our insurance coverage is still valid.  There is no change in
coverage.  It's the same, but
we will have a debt on
our insurance and it will be subject to the
interest rate.  It can be paid
anytime.  That's called an automatic
premium loan.  Remember, if
our insurance debt is greater
than our cash values,
our insurance
plan will automatically terminate.  Number three, surrender or
terminate our insurance plan and
we will receive the cash
surrender values ​​that are in
our policy.  The amount depends on how
much we have paid and how
many years we have had our policy.  That's
called cash surrender value.
Number eight that we should know is
contestability.  If within
two years of taking out
our insurance plan, a claim has been made
, FWD can contest it
if there is a violation found in the
application we made.  If it is
proven that we lied and
hid important
information,
our insurance plan will lose its validity.  Let's talk about
the advantages that
I personally saw in this product.  Number one
is his major critical illness benefit
which can be claimed up to three times
.  Number two is
his minor critical illness benefit of 20% which
will not be deducted from the major critical illness
benefit.  Number three,
payments will stop.
In the event of a major critical
illness benefit claim.  Life
insurance is still active even if
the major critical illness benefit has been claimed
up to age 75. Number five, there is an
opportunity to get back everything
we have invested if we do not have a
major critical illness claim.  I
believe that even if we have a plan like this,
we still don't want to get sick.
We would still prefer to
live long and healthy lives.  So it's just like a
reverse bet.  It's really a gamble.  Number
six, there are cash values ​​that can
serve as a safety net.  In case
we no longer need this insurance
and want to terminate it,
we will at least have some way to get a refund.
Number seven,
his benefits are guaranteed such as life insurance,
critical illness insurance, and cash
values.  Number eight, he has
exclusive rewards for digital
products.  Number one is free FWD
Security Bank Card.  You will have a
bank account at Security Bank.  It's free to turn
on.  Number two, unlimited free
consultation at The Medical City.
Remember, this is not part of the contract.  These
are just freebies so they may
change from time to time.  Advantage number nine
is that its payment period is flexible
because we can pay for 5
years, 10 years, and 20 years.  Number
10, the payment mode is flexible.  So
we can pay this quarterly,
semi-annually
or annually.  And if there are advantages,
we also see
disadvantages.  Number one,
its premium is higher versus other life
insurance products.  Therefore, not
everyone can avail of
this product.  Only those people with consistent
extra funds are capable of acquiring and
sustaining this product.  Number
two, his life insurance and critical
illness benefits are not flexible.
He is packaged.  Life and critical
illness coverage are equal.  Unlike
other products, you can increase
life insurance coverage over critical
illness coverage.  Depends on the protection
you need.  Number three
disadvantage.  Even if what
we lost at age 75 comes back, the value won't be as
high during that time
because of inflation.  1 million 20
years ago is different from 1 million today and
1 million in the next 20 years will be different.  Who is
this product for?  Number one, for
bread winners, those with dependents,
there are people who depend on them.  Number
two is for people who don't want to ask for
help from family or other people
if something happens to them.  For
people with incomes higher than
those of minimum wage earners.  Number
four, for those who are clear that
this is an insurance plan, not
savings
and not an investment.  Number five,
for people who are willing to commit
long-term to this product.  Before you
get life insurance, consider
these first.  Number one, know for
sure if you really need
life insurance.  Number two, what
plan and coverage do you need?
Number three, do you really have enough
budget for your life insurance?
If you think you're ready, how can you
avail it?  Number one, approach
the insurance agent you know
from FWD.  Number two, visit the
nearest FWD branch in your area.
Number three.  Number three, if you don't
need and don't want the
guidance of an insurance advisor
because you already know what you're doing,
you can avail it online.
The product link is in the caption.
That goes straight to the specific product that is
our topic in this video.  If
you would like more comprehensive
information about insurance or feel
you need to speak with us
personally about your insurance policy,
just email us at
realtins01@gmail.com.
I hope you learned something from
this video.